fun2cell.net 2016-01-17

# Fun2cell UK :: Privacy policy

| 

## Privacy policy

This website and WAP site (the "Sites") are owned and operated by the Provider ("we," "our" or "us"). By using the Sites and the Service (defined below), you agree to the collection and use of your information by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, then do not use the services supplied via the internet, the Sites or Providers online and mobile entertainment and information short messaging services (the "Service"). This Privacy Policy is applicable to use of the Sites and the Service, including but not limited to, all new facilities constituting any expansion or improvement of the Service, such as the release of new functions. 

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Service following any changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes. 

## Information We Collect

We collect and process "personal information" (i.e. information that could be used to contact you, such as full name, postal address, phone number, e-mail address, MSISDN (mobile station integrated services digital network number), "financial information" (i.e. bank account information) or "demographic and usage information" (i.e. information that you submit, or that we collect, that is neither personal information nor financial information but necessary for the proper functioning and billing of our Service, such as the date regarding the start and end and the extent of your usage of the Service, the type of browser you are using, web browsing patterns and IP address), in connection with the Service. We may pass on your personal information, financial information and or demographic and usage information ("the Information"), to your carrier to secure collection of fees and such information collected by Provider may be stored and processed in the country in which Provider or its agents maintain facilities. By using the Service, you consent to any such transfer of Information outside of your country. The Information will be deleted no later than 6 months after termination of your subscription. Provider may store the Information beyond this date if that is required by law or contract. 

## How We Use Your Information

Provider supplies you with an extensive collection of online and mobile entertainment and informational content via the Service. We will use your personally identifiable information to deliver the Service and for customer service. Your personally identifiable information is used by us to respond to your requests, process your transactions for the Service, and send you information about Service benefits, improvements and promotions via text messaging. Unless you tell us not to, we may use your personally identifiable information to contact you about programs, products, features or services in which we believe you may be interested (such as future promotional materials). Also may use your personally identifiable information to contact you regarding your use of the Sites and/or Services or changes to our Privacy Policy, General Terms and Conditions, Specific Terms and Conditions, or other policies or terms that affect you and your use of our Sites and/or Services. In addition, we may use information collected about you to improve the content and navigation of our Sites, or for other internal purposes. 

In addition to our service providers and third party contractors specified herein, we may also share your personally identifiable information with other third party marketers and business partners who may contact you regarding their products and services and who may want to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. Some jurisdictions do not allow us to send text message advertisements without your express consent, so the foregoing may not apply to you. 

If you would like to opt-out of our sharing your personal information with those third party marketers and business partners for marketing purposes, indicate that we may not do so at the point where you give us such personal information. If you change your mind later, you can send an e-mail to the address as stated to you on the Sites and/or through our Services. Also, the telephone number, which number you can find in the Specific Terms, can be called and we will no longer share your personal information with these third parties. Please note that deletions of your personal information or changes in your preferences may not be effective immediately and will be effective for the purpose of managing future communications only. 

We use non-personally identifiable information for internal purposes and to help us administer the Service and interact with visitors to the Sites. We may also share non-personally identifiable information in the aggregate form with third parties to illustrate trends and patterns. We may also use non-personally identifiable information to personalize and customize the content of the Service for you and send you targeted ads based on keyword searches. We may also combine the information we collect with third parties or publicly available information. 

When you sign up for the Service or use other features of the Service, we collect your mobile telephone number and the identity of your mobile telephone service provider. Charges for the Service will be billed directly to your mobile telephone service account. By purchasing the Service, you consent to our providing your mobile telephone number to our service providers and to such third parties as we determine is necessary to process your transactions. These third parties may include the carriers used to process the transaction. 

We may use third party contractors to help us operate our business, the Service and administer activities on our behalf, such as authorization of mobile telephone bill transactions, and may share your information with these contractors for those limited purposes. 

If Provider is sold to, or merges with, another company, or declares bankruptcy, some or all of the information collected from you may be transferred to a third party as a result of the transfer of assets or bankruptcy event. We may also disclose your information when we determine it is necessary to comply with applicable laws or protect the interests or safety of Provider or users of the Service. 

## Cookies

To enhance your experience with our Sites, we may use cookies on the website. We use cookies to understand Site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our Sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web- or WAP pages (e.g., to recognize you when you return to our Site). You may adjust your browser to reject cookies from us or from any other web- or WAP site. Please consult the Help section of your browser for more information. However, certain areas of our Sites can be accessed only in conjunction with cookies or similar devices and you should be aware that disabling cookies or similar devices might prevent you from accessing some of our content. 

## Adults Only

Neither the Service nor the Sites are intended for use by children. We will not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information submitted by users who have not reached the age as described in the Terms and Conditions. 

## Links

The Sites may contain links to other web- or WAP sites. Provider does not control such other web- and WAP sites and is not responsible or liable for the availability thereof or the content, advertising, products or other materials contained on such sites. Provider shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss incurred or suffered by any user in connection therewith. Your access and use of linked sites, including the content therein, is solely at your own risk. 

## Security

Protecting your information is important to us. We use the industry standard technology to protect the security of your information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet and via mobile communications networks can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we are committed to protecting your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or through us. 

## Accessing Your Information

Provider gives you the opportunity to review and remove personal information that you have provided to us or change your preferences. You can send an e-mail to the address that you can find on the Sites and/or through our Services or you can call us at the telephone number, which you can find in the Specific Terms and state whether you want your information removed from our database, if you want to opt-out of communications from us or if you want to opt-out of communications from third party marketers or business partners. Deleting your information or otherwise opting-out of receipt of communications from Provider or third parties will delete the data only in our database for purposes of managing future communications from Provider and third parties. These deletions will not delete information already collected that may have already been shared with third parties, all as provided above in this Privacy Policy. You will need to contact third parties that may contact you directly to delete your personal information that they may be using to contact you.   
  
---|---
